question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {"type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Vietnam's national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
         },
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}
